studica.com 2017-12-27

# Privacy Policy

We (Studica, Inc.) are committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring that your use of www.studica.com ("Website") is as secure and enjoyable as possible. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect information from you during your use of the Website, and how we use that information.

What we collect

If you register for an account, then we will collect personal information from you, including your name, email address, phone number, billing address, shipping address, and school/employer information. We do not store your credit card information. Since payments are collected via PayPal, your credit card information will not be transferred to us but will instead be held by, and subject to the terms of use and privacy policy of, PayPal.

Your use of the Website will be done anonymously unless you have logged into your account. We may log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of how you use the Website, but we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged into your account. We may use "cookies" to understand your use of the Website and improve your experience (see "Cookies" below).

How we use your personal information

We may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To respond to requests for information or services.
  * To permit you to interact with other users.
  * To confirm your identity.
  * To provide customer support.
  * To verify your status for discounts.

Who we share it with

We never sell or rent your personal information; we may disclose your personal information to third-party service providers (but only to the extent that such disclosure is needed) or if required to do so by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation, or in good faith to (a) comply with legal processes served on the site, or (b) protect the rights and property of Studica, or (c) where our records indicate fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of, or (d) where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

In the event that Studica, or any operation thereunder, is transferred or sold, we reserve the right to transfer your personal information to the entity or entities that have taken control of or purchased Studica. If that happens, the new entity or entities will adhere to a privacy policy that is at least as stringent as this policy.

Security of your Personal Information

Your personal information is never shared with outside parties without your permission, except under conditions explained above, and data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Our Website uses secure socket layer ("SSL") encryption to protect your personal information whenever it is collected or transmitted.

No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others. If you believe that an unauthorized person has gained access to your username and/or password, please notify us immediately by contacting us.

Access to your Personal Information

You may review and update your personal information at any time by contacting us.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to your data.

Use of Analytics

Our Website does generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to the Website. This information is used for internal purposes only. The statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

The Website uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Website or our services.

We also use third party analytic services that may collect personal information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you've visited our Website. When an order is shipped, certain information may be collected including IP address, name, last four digits of your social security number (for eligibility verification), email address, order number, order items and order total. Some services may monitor more in-depth page activities such as user clicks, user scrolls, and keyboard strokes. We strongly recommend that you review those parties' terms of use and privacy policies, and the third parties that we are currently associated with are Google: Analytics, Trusted Store, Ad Services; Janrain, Convert, Global Rekko, Shopping.com, PriceGrabber, Commission Junction, ShareASale, Microsoft, Bing, CPC Strategy, Bronto, CrazyEgg, and SheerID.

Changes to Privacy Policy; California Online Privacy Protection Act

In the event that we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a message on the Website alerting you that changes have been made.

Because we value your privacy we have taken steps to comply with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. If you would like to review and/or modify the personal information that we have on file for you, please contact us.

Do Not Track

While Studica does understand DNT legislation, we do not currently offer a "do not track" option at this time. Please review our Privacy Policy in its entirety to understand how your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is collected, for what purpose and for further information on what third parties are given access to.

Problems or complaints with Our Privacy Policy

We value your comments and opinions. If you have questions, comments or a complaint about compliance with this privacy policy you may contact us.
